{
	"questions": [
		{
			"id": 1,
			"question": "For certain services like Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS), you can invest in reserved capacity. What options are available for Reserved Instances? (Choose three.)",
			"options": ["AURI", "MURI", "NURI", "PURI", "DURI"],
			"correctAnswers": [0, 2, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 2,
			"question": "Where can a customer go to get more details about Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) billing activity that took place 3 months ago? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Amazon EC2 dashboard",
				"AWS Cost Explorer",
				"AWS Trusted Advisor dashboard",
				"AWS CloudTrail logs stored in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 3,
			"question": "True or false? To receive the discounted rate associated with Reserved Instances, you must make a full, upfront payment for the term of the agreement.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 4,
			"question": "Which statement is true about the pricing model on AWS? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"In most cases, there is a per gigabyte charge for inbound data transfer.",
				"Storage is typically charged per gigabyte.",
				"Compute is typically charged as a monthly fee based on instance type.",
				"Outbound charges are free up to a per account limit."
			],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 5,
			"question": "What are the four support plans offered by AWS Support? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Basic, Developer, Business, Enterprise",
				"Basic, Startup, Business, Enterprise",
				"Free, Bronze, Silver, Gold",
				"All support is free"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 6,
			"question": "What AWS tool lets you explore AWS services and create an estimate for the cost of your use cases on AWS? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"AWS Pricing Calculator",
				"AWS Budgets",
				"AWS Cost and Usage Report",
				"AWS Billing Dashboard"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 7,
			"question": "As AWS grows, the cost of doing business is reduced and savings are passed back to the customer with lower pricing. What is this optimization called? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Expenditure awareness",
				"Economies of scale",
				"Matching supply and demand",
				"EC2 Right Sizing"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 8,
			"question": "True or false? AWS offers some services at no charge (for example, Amazon VPC, IAM, Consolidated Billing, Elastic Beanstalk, Auto Scaling, OpsWorks, CloudFormation). However, you might be charged for other AWS services that you use in conjunction with these services.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 9,
			"question": "What are benefits of using AWS Organizations? (Choose two.)",
			"options": [
				"Replaces existing AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies with service control policies (SCPs), which are simpler to manage",
				"Provides the ability to create groups of accounts and then attach policies to a group",
				"Provides the ability to create an unlimited number of nested organizational units (OUs) to support your desired structure",
				"Simplifies automating account creation and management by using APIs",
				"Prevents any restrictions from being put on the root user that is associated with the main organization in an account"
			],
			"correctAnswers": [1, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 10,
			"question": "True or false? Unlimited services are available with the AWS Free Tier to new AWS customers for 12 months following their AWS sign-up date.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 11,
			"question": "Which component of the AWS Global Infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"AWS Regions",
				"AWS edge locations",
				"AWS Availability Zones",
				"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 12,
			"question": "You can run applications and workloads from a Region closer to the end users to ______ latency.",
			"options": ["increase", "decrease"],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 13,
			"question": "True or False? Networking, storage, compute, and databases are examples of service categories that AWS offers.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 14,
			"question": "Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"AWS Origins",
				"AWS Regions",
				"Compute zones",
				"Edge locations"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 15,
			"question": "_____ means the infrastructure has built-in component redundancy and _____ means that resources dynamically adjust to increases or decreases in capacity requirements.",
			"options": [
				"No human intervention, fault tolerant",
				"Elastic and scalable, no human intervention",
				"Fault tolerant, elastic and scalable",
				"Fault tolerant, no human intervention",
				"Elastic and scalable, fault tolerant"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id": 16,
			"question": "True or False? Availability Zones within a Region are connected through low-latency links.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 17,
			"question": "Which of these statements about Availability Zones is not true? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Availability Zones are designed for fault isolation.",
				"Availability Zones are made up of one or more data centers.",
				"A data center can be used for more than one Availability Zone.",
				"Availability Zones are connected to each other using high-speed private links."
			],
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id": 18,
			"question": "What is true about Regions? (Choose two.)",
			"options": [
				"Each Region is located in a separate geographic area.",
				"They are the physical locations of your customers.",
				"All Regions are located in one specific geographic area.",
				"A Region is a physical location that has multiple Availability Zones."
			],
			"correctAnswers": [0, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 19,
			"question": "AWS highly recommends provisioning your compute resources across ______ Availability Zones. (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": ["all", "no", "multiple", "single"],
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id": 20,
			"question": "True or False? Edge locations are only located in the same general area as Regions.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 21,
			"question": "In the shared responsibility model, AWS is responsible for providing what? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Security of the cloud",
				"Security to the cloud",
				"Security for the cloud",
				"Security in the cloud"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 22,
			"question": "In the shared responsibility model, which of the following are examples of `security in the cloud`? (Choose two.)",
			"options": [
				"Compliance with compute security standards and regulations",
				"Physical security of the facilities in which the services operate",
				"Security group configurations",
				"Encryption of data at rest and data in transit",
				"Protecting the global infrastructure"
			],
			"correctAnswers": [2, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 23,
			"question": "Which of the following is the responsibility of AWS under the AWS shared responsibility model? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Configuring third-party applications",
				"Maintaining physical hardware",
				"Security application access and data",
				"Managing custom Amazon Machine Images (AMIs)"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 24,
			"question": "When creating an AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policy, what are the two types of access that can be granted to a user? (Choose two.)",
			"options": [
				"Institutional access",
				"Authorized access",
				"Programmatic access",
				"AWS Management Console access",
				"Administrative root access"
			],
			"correctAnswers": [2, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 25,
			"question": "True or False? AWS Organizations enables you to consolidate multiple AWS accounts so that you centrally manage them.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"id": 26,
			"question": "Which of the following are best practices to secure your account using AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)? (Choose two.)",
			"options": [
				"Provide users with default administrative privileges.",
				"Leave unused and unnecessary users and credentials in place.",
				"Manage access to AWS resources.",
				"Avoid using IAM groups to grant the same access permissions to multiple users.",
				"Define fine-grained access rights."
			],
			"correctAnswers": [2, 4]
		},
		{
			"id": 27,
			"question": "Which of the following should be done by the AWS account root user? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Secure access for applications",
				"Integrate with other AWS services",
				"Change granular permissions",
				"Change the AWS support plan"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 3
		},
		{
			"id": 28,
			"question": "After initial login, what does AWS recommend as the best practice for the AWS account root user? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Delete the AWS account root user",
				"Revoke all permissions on the AWS account root user",
				"Restrict permission on the AWS account root user",
				"Delete the access keys of the AWS account root user"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 3
		},
		{
			"id": 29,
			"question": "How would a system administrator add an additional layer of login security to a user's AWS Management Console? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": [
				"Use Amazon Cloud Directory",
				"Audit AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles",
				"Enable multi-factor authentication",
				"Enable AWS CloudTrail"
			],
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id": 30,
			"question": "True or False? AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) enables you to assess, audit, and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources.",
			"options": ["True", "False"],
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id": 31,
			"question": "With Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC), what is the smallest size subnet you can have in a VPC? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": ["/26", "/30", "/28", "/24"],
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id": 32,
			"question": "With Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC), what is the maximum size IP address range you can have in a VPC? (Select the best answer.)",
			"options": ["/16", "/24", "/30", "/28"],
			"correctAnswer": 0
		}
	]
}
